A Guide to the American Chemical Society Virginia Section records, 1927-2001
Library of Virginia
- Series VIII: General files, 1932-2001., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 25-34)
  - It's Your Society, 1947, 1964. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Awards booklets, 1961 (2 copies), 1964, no date. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Booklets on student affiliation, no date. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Chemistry and Chemists and Publicizing the Chemical Profession, 1964 and no date. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Charles F. Spencer Award. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Distinguished Service Award, 1962. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Distinguished Service Award, 1964. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Awards to college students, 1976. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - American Chemical Society meeting, 1932. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - American Chemical Society meetings, 1942-1943. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - American Chemical Society meeting, 1948. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - American Chemical Society council meeting, 4 April 1976. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - American Chemical Society council meeting, 1 September 1976. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - American Chemical Society council meeting, 23 March 1977. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - American Chemical Society council meeting, 31 August 1977. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - American Chemical Society council meeting, 26 March 1980. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - American Chemical Society council meeting, 27 August 1980. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - American Chemical Society southeast regional meeting steering committee, 1973-1974. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - American Chemical Society southeastern regional meeting, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Section meeting, 1942. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Section meetings, 1976. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Roster additions, 1973-1974. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Roster, 1980. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Chemical defenses, 1942-1943. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Science bills, 1945-1946. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Action required, 1948-1949. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Radio, 1949. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Richmond area scientists dinner, 1964. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Presentation of 50 year membership certificates, 1964. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Fiftieth anniversary celebration, 1964. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - History of Virgnia Section, 1965. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Councilors certification, 1975-1980. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Academy of Science certificate, 1976. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Technical training in Virginia, 1964. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - American Chemical Society--Virginia Section Presented to Governor Baliles,, 14 July 1986. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Chemical and Engineering News editorial policy on local section news, 1964. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Institute for Scientific Research. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Technical Notes and Data on Civilian Protection Against Gas. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Guidelines for employment. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Mailing permits, 1977. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - The New Chemistry,1976. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977. (Box 34, Folder 18)